NAA Additional Files Regarding Proceedings 5985
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
NAA Additional Files Regarding Proceedings
1987-1994
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
National Academy of Arbitrators (NAA)
5985
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
5745665
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, September 19, 2011
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 24, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5796: NAA Additional Records 5775: NAA Records 6004: NAA Additional Records 6004 AV: NAA Audio-Visual Material 6004 OHM: NAA History Committee Oral History Interview Masters 6004 OHT: NAA History Committee Oral History Interview Transcripts 6205: NAA Committee Files 5246: NAA Records 5246: NAA Records 6136: Dennis Nolan Collection of National Academy of Arbitrators History Files
Professional associations -- United States; Trade associations -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; National Academy of Arbitrators
5745665
- Corres. Proceedings 1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 1993 Proceedings Correspondence. (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Proceedings 1991 NAA (Box 1, Folder 3)
- 1992 Proceedings Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 4)
- 1990 Proceedings Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 1987-1989 Proceedings Corres. (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Edited Manuscript from 1991 NAA Proceedings [folder 1 of 4] (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Edited Manuscript from 1991 NAA Proceedings [folder 2 of 4] (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Edited Manuscript from 1991 NAA Proceedings [folder 3 of 4] (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Edited Manuscript from 1991 NAA Proceedings [folder 4 of 4] (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Edited Manuscript from 1994 NAA Proceedings [folder 1 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Edited Manuscript from 1994 NAA Proceedings [folder 2 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 12)